孩子们 维持良好关系 关键是要懂得交流
Kids, the key to a good relationship is communication.
- 你得懂得去说 - 去咪咪饭店吃饭怎么样?
- You need to talk. - How about Mimi's?
我不太想去那吃
Nah, I don't really feel like Mimi's.
我饿了 我们找个地方 去吃点东西
Well, I'm hungry. Let's just pick a place and go.
去森雅斯 怎么样?
Oh, you know where we should go? Cynthia's.
你很喜欢那里 记得我们在那里度过的美好时光?
You love that place-- remember what a great time we had
上一次在那里的时候
the last time we were there?
我们? 是啊
- We did? - Yeah, yeah.
有个有趣的服务生不停的说 "你们两个应该结婚"
We had that crazy waiter who kept going, "You two should get married!
"你们两个应该结婚"
You two should get married!"
知道什么时候 应该闭嘴也很重要
It's also important to know when to stop talking.
想起了吗?然后我们就 走到了外面  外面正在下雨
Come on. Then we stepped outside. It was raining.
很浪漫?
It was so romantic?
你怎么能够把这些忘了?
How can you not remember this?
因为和你一起去的那个人不是我
Because it wasn't me.
对...对...
Oh, right!
那个人是...
It was...
我妹妹
my sister.
你们知道  20多岁最难忘的就是
You see, by the time you've hit your late 20s,
和好多人曾经约会过
you've dated a few people,
但是当你正在和一个人谈恋爱时
but when you're in a relationship, it's common courtesy to pretend
最好装作你毫无恋爱经验
that you haven't.
在播范海辛
Oh, my God, Van Helsing is on.
记得我们一起看过这部片子?
Remember when we went to see it?
我们是坐在后排看的
We sat in the back row.
我从来没有看过范海辛
I've never seen Van Helsing.
想起来了 是和我妹妹一起去看的
That's right. I saw it with my sister.
我老板刚刚从毛伊岛回来
My boss just got back from Maui.
他说那里很浪漫
He said it was really romantic.
那里是不错
Oh, it's so romantic.
你什么时候去过毛伊岛?
When were you in Maui?
- 我是和...我妹妹一起的 - 和我妹妹
- I... went... with my sister. - With my sister.
你为什么总是说和你妹妹一起?
Why do you always say that?
我们都是成年人了 和别人约会过是很正常的事情
Look, we're not 16. We've both dated other people.
你为什么总要装作没有过?
It's silly to try to act like we didn't.
你说得对
You're right.
我不应该撒谎
We should just be honest.
完全不应该!
Totally.
看见坐在那里的女孩了?
See that girl over there?
三年前 我曾经追过她
Three years ago, I totally made out with her.
我不想听这个
I don't want to hear that.
- 什么?你说过... - 你这个人毫不知趣
- What? You said... - God, that is so insensitive.
- 你说过要诚实 - 你这个混蛋
- Remember honesty...? - You're a jerk!
你...
Well, you're...
真让人捉摸不透
confusing.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www  YYETS  com
Transcript : Raceman Subtitles : Willow's Team
老爸老妈的浪漫史
第二季 第十七集
翻译：    Eva-cao    校对：     傻瓜都一样
后期：     oliver0951      字幕监制：  叶煦
如果你不得不和某人上床
Okay, so you have to have sex with one.
你是选择人脸鱼身的古典美人鱼
Either classic mermaid; bottom half fish, top half human,
还是鱼脸人身的美人鱼?
or inverted mermaid, top half fish, bottom half human.
快说
Go!
我不知道 她胖吗?
I don't know. Is she fat?
美人鱼毕竟是鱼  当然丰满了
Yeah, but it's a fish, so it's the good kind of fat.
最新消息
Hot off the presses!
我不要广告宣传单
I-I don't take flyers.
你只要一会就走到那里了
You took one two seconds before you walked in here.
那不一样 我去看脱衣服走得通常很快
That's different. It was for a strip club.
如同装了一对翅膀
Two bucks off wings.
你宣传单上的演出有那么吸引我?
How much is your flyer going to save me on wings?
这是关于我演出的宣传单
Fine. It's a flyer from my play.
莉莉 我很想去 但是我们已经不是学生时代了
Oh, Lily, I'd love to, but we're not in college
我不会和你上床的
and I'm not trying to sleep with you.
- 所以无论如何 这条美人鱼... - 莉莉的朋友邀请她参加演出
- So anyway, this mermaid... - Hey, Lily's friend asked her
演出会很精彩
to be in this play, and it's gonna be really good.
莉莉 我很仰慕你 但是我们都过了这个年龄了
Lily, I love you, but we're too old for this.
让别人去看你的演出
Asking someone to come see your play
就如同让别人开车送你去机场
is like asking someone for a ride to the airport
或是让他抱你到沙发上 或让他帮你搬家
or to crash on your couch or to help you move.
叫个司机 订个房间 雇些搬运工 跟着我说
Call a cab, book a room,
再雇些搬运工 跟在我后面不停的说
hire some movers and repeat after me:
"朋友不会强迫他朋友去看糟糕表演的"
Friends don't let friends come see their crappy play.
首先 我会考虑 选择鱼面人身美人鱼
Okay, first of all, I've thought about it and top half fish.
第二  需要你们 帮我和罗宾决定一件事情
Second of all, we need you guys to decide something for us.
是的  你们应该分手
Yes, you should break up.
今晚发生了件事情
So, earlier tonight...
我看我们应该去酒吧了
Mm, we should get down to the bar.
我知道
I know we should,
但你穿着我的红色运动服好性感
but you just look so sexy in my red sweatshirt.
干吗说这个?
Oh, God, why is this part of the story?
故事还没有完
We're getting to it.
该死的 我的脸好干 这里有润肤露?
Damn, my face is so dry. Is there any moisturizer around here?
卫生间里应该有
Yeah, there's some in the bathroom.
去拿润肤露
Got to moisturize!
让那俊俏的小脸更加滋润
Got to keep that pretty face moist.
不...不...不!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- 她怎么了? - 她讨厌那个词
- What's wrong with her? - She hates that word.
- 哪个词?'湿润'? - 快给我闭嘴!
- What word, "moist"? - No! Seriously, stop!
然后泰德去卫生间里给我拿...
So, anyway, Ted goes into the bathroom to get the moist...
润肤露...
face lotion...
这东西不错
Wow, this is great stuff.
我知道你皮肤好的秘诀了
Now I know the secret to your great complexion.
你在说什么?这润肤露是你的
What are you talking about? It's yours.
不  不是我的
No, it's not.
那可能是莉莉的
Oh, well... then I guess it's Lily's.
也不是我的
No, it's not.
润肤露究竟是谁的?
Whose moisturizer is this, Ted?
是我妹妹的...
Um, my sister's.
换句话说 它是 和你约会的某个女生的
So, in other words, some girl you went out with.
啊...我爱你 亲爱的
Um... I love you.
真恶心! 你竟然让我用你前任女友的润肤露
Disgusting. You let me put on the same moisturizer as one of your exes?
可能是卡尔的 她的皮肤很糟糕
It was probably Carla's. Her face was a train wreck.
泰德又不是和她的脸约会
I'm don't think Ted was dating her for her face.
多谢 马修
Thank you, Marshall.
十分感谢
Thank you so much.
为什么它还在你的屋子里?
Why is that still in your apartment?
我不知道啊 可能是我从来没有把它扔掉
I don't know. I just never threw it out.
为什么不扔掉? 你对她还念念不忘?
Well, why not? Do you still have feelings for this girl?
是的  我疯狂的爱着她
Yeah. I'm madly in love with her,
而且我唯一可以做的
and the only way I can deal with it
就是寄情于一只3美元的润肤露
is by holding onto a three-dollar tube of lotion.
3美元!怎么不说是14美元!
Not three dollars! Try 14.
你干吗这么生气?
Why is this such a big deal?
因为我不想用妓女的润肤露!
Because I don't want to use some whore's moisturizer!
她不是妓女
Whoa, she wasn't a whore.
如果一个女人用过的润肤露 满城都能找到
Well, she's leaving expensive lotions all over town.
对于我来说  她就是妓女
It sounds like a whore to me.
你还留着前任女友的 其他什么东西?
What else do you have from old girlfriends just lying around?
没有了  就这个
Nothing. That's it.
除了那个电话亭
Well, except for the phone booth.
桌子旁边的灯
And the lamp by the desk...
还有...
and the...
不...
No.
不...不...不! 泰德
No! No! Oh, Ted!
还是个老问题
Ah, the age-old question:
一旦你和某人分手 你该如何处理那些东西
after you break up with someone, what do you do with the stuff?
问题?那不应该是问题
Question? Ain't no question, girl.
很显然 他应该把那些都扔了
Obviously, he's got to get rid of it.
那显然很疯狂 而且我显然不会那么做
Which is obviously crazy and obviously, I'm not gonna do it.
所以我们同意 让你们帮我们拿主意
So we agreed that we would let you guys decide.
就像我们处理马修的裤子那样
Yeah, like we did with Marshall's pants.
2005年轰动的案例 莉莉对决乔伊・布塔弗科裤子
Ah, the 2005 landmark case of Lily v. The Joey Buttafuoco Pants.
不错  是吧?
Nice, right?
我觉得不怎么好
I'm gonna have to say no.
我可不会让一个16岁的女孩爱上你
I don't want some 16-year-old girl falling in love with you
让莉莉伤心
and then shooting Lily in the face.
太好了
Yes!
我认为那女生会和他在一起
I vote they can stay.
因为穿着迷彩服去结账是很少见的
"Check out the jackass in the parachute pants" is a good icebreaker.
泰德
T ed.
泰德 泰德 你说说看
Ted? Ted?
不好意思 我也觉得不行
Sorry, buddy, it's a "no" for me, too.
顺便说一下 贝尔声称
Oh, and by the way, Bel Biv Devoe called.
他们也不会如此打扮了
Even they don't want those pants back.
它们穿起来很舒服
They were insanely comfortable!
就像可以穿出门的睡衣
They were like pajamas you could wear outside.
这些都过去了
Marshall, it's over.
我们甚至还帮你瞧了瞧 配上军靴还是不好看
We even gave you an appeal and they didn't look any better with combat boots.
外面听听他们的争论 泰德 你先说
All right, well, let's hear the arguments. Ted, you go first.
我还留着前任女友的东西 不值得大惊小怪
Okay. The fact that I still have things from ex-girlfriends is no big deal.
我的意思是说 当我看到钢琴上的电话亭时
I mean, when I see the phone booth on the piano,
我并没有想到吉莉
I don't think of Jeannie Radford,
想到的是 在欧洲旅游时候的快乐时光
I think of the good times I had backpacking through Europe.
当我看到台灯时 我没有想到爱丽舍
And when I see the lamp, I don't think of Allison Moses.
我想到大学毕业后 我穷困潦倒的时候
I remember when I was broke, just out of college,
我需要一盏台灯
and I really needed a lamp.
当我看到抱枕时 我没有想到劳恩
And when I see that throw pillow, I don't think of Lauren Stein.
我想到的是上面那桔红色污点 以及是如何弄上去的
I think of that weird orange-brown stain and how it got there.
都是些意外之财
Creamsicle and turkey gravy,
不同时候的意外之财
not at the same time.
不错  那些是很可爱
Well, that's adorable,
但是从现在起 当我走进公寓 我看到的是...
but from now on, when I walk into the apartment, here is what I will see.
我是泰德的大学女友 他曾经给我做了12盘混音磁带
I'm Ted's college girlfriend. He made me 12 mix tapes.
他给你做过多少?
How many has he made you?
他叫你'甜心派'?
He calls you "sweetie pie"?
他就是这么叫我的
He called me "sweetie pie."
我不聪明 但是我的胸部比你大
I'm stupid, but my rack is bigger than yours.
真的? 你不能这么下结论
Really? You can't look at a pillow
仅仅看到一个抱枕而没有看到真人 那只是抱枕!
without seeing my ex-girlfriend-- a pillow!
事实是那个抱枕很恶心!
Yes, Ted, the fact that you still have that pillow is creepy and gross.
- 你才恶心! - 你妈才恶心!
- You're creepy and gross. - Your mom's creepy and gross.
肃静! 肃静!
Order! Order!
我站在罗宾这边
I got to side with Robin.
她现在是你的女友 她觉得不爽的东西 你就应该扔了
She's your girlfriend, and if the stuff upsets her, you got to get rid of it.
我支持泰德
I've got to side with Ted.
留着前任女友的东西
Just 'cause you still have something an ex-girlfriend gave you
并不意味着你还想着她
doesn't mean you're holding onto her.
好了 巴尼
All right, Barney.
该你说了
It all comes down to you.
- 我支持罗宾 - 什么?
- I side with Robin. - What?
你那地方太乱了
Ted, your place is too cluttered.
和住在本尼根餐厅差不了多少
It's like you're living in a Bennigan's.
或者在丹比店里
Or a Danby's.
什么?美国没有丹比吗?
What, they don't have Danby's in the US?
真的?
Really?
那你们吃过掌印冰淇淋三明治吗?
Well, then were do you get Grizzly Paw ice cream sandwiches?
别说了 亲爱的
Just stop, sweetie.
我别无他法
So I had no choice.
只得把我前任女友的 所有东西打包
I packed up everything I had gotten from ex-girlfriends.
万分痛苦
It was painful,
但那晚更痛苦
but not as painful as what I had to endure later that night.
纽约以戏剧而出名
New York is famous for its theater,
但是戏剧水平也是分档次的
but there's many different levels.
那里有百老汇级别的
There's Broadway,
稍次于百老汇的
off-Broadway,
比百老汇差多了的
off-off-Broadway,
无家可归的人在公园里尖叫
homeless people screaming in the park,
紧接着就轮到莉莉的表演
and then below that, the play Aunt Lily was in.
八楼
Eight flights, of stairs.
什么剧院会建在八楼?
Who puts a theater up eight flights of stairs?
这是个什么建筑?
What kind of building is this?
闻这味道 估计以前是个工厂
From the smell of it, I'm guessing a urine factory.
我们该坐哪?
Where do you guys want to sit?
我知道我不想坐哪
I know where I don't want to sit.
这里有四个连一起的位置
Guys, four together!
我带了个口袋  以防看得会吐了
I brought a bag in case anyone needs to puke.
快点 我看没那么糟吧
Come on. It's not gonna be that bad.
没那么糟? 好吧 就当我没说
No? Okay.
我..是...愤怒
I... am... Rage!
我...是...贪婪
I... am Greed.
我是愤怒... 不 是嫉妒
I am Rage... Envy!
我想走了
I am outta here.
不行 你得留下来
No, you're not. You have to stay.
这是物欲的嘴脸
This is the face of Consumerism!
泰德也成戏中的角色了
Oh, my God. Ted's part of the play.
你们好 贪婪 愤怒...
Hello, Greed, Rage...
嫉妒...
Envy...
还有物欲
and Consumerism.
我..是你们的父亲...
I... am your father...
美国!
America!
亲爱的 你演得太棒了
Oh, baby, that was wonderful!
我完全没有料到贪婪是凶手
Totally, I had no idea Greed was the killer.
当我参加表演
And when it became a play within a play,
我会像这样 '现在我们都醉了'
I was, like, "Now we are really cookin'!"
你们演得太差劲了!
Wow, Lily, that sucked!
巴尼!
Barney!
怎么了?是很糟糕啊
What? It was terrible.
我的意思是... 伙计们 你们都同意我说的 是吗?
I mean, come on. You guys agree, right?
不好意思 我一向很坦白 '因为我们是朋友'
Hey, sorry, I'm just being honest 'cause, you know, we're friends.
朋友应该让别人开心
No, friends make each other feel good.
他们站在背后 支持着朋友
They build each other up and support them.
这才是朋友该做的!
That's what being a good friend is about.
如果你是蓝精灵 我会那么做
Yeah, if you're a Smurf.
如果你表演 我会一直坐在那里看
You know if you did a play, I would sit through the whole thing
而且看完也不会抱怨什么
and I would compliment you on it afterwards.
真的吗? 你真的会那样?
Oh, really? You would?
当然
Yes.
真是让人感动
Bad move, Aldrin, bad move.
五分钟后 将在这里进行导演观众见面会
We'll be starting our Q&A with the director--
你们真诚的...
yours truly--
in five minutes right here.
你能想像刚才 巴尼说的那些话
Can you believe Barney said that about Lily's play?
那家伙说话不经大脑思考
I know. He can be really insensitive.
他说的那话很糟糕
It was pretty bad, though.
是的 糟糕透了
Oh, my God, it was so bad.
你家遭打劫了?
Oh, my God, you've been robbed!
不是!
Nope.
你把前任女友送的东西都丢了?
All that stuff was from old girlfriends?
你都不帮自己买东西的?
Don't you buy anything for yourself?
该怎么说呢...
What can I say?
那些东西都是可有可无的
Papa gets swag.
这个故事本该结束了 但是第二天...
And that should've been the end of it. But the next day...
刚扔掉我的那些东西时 我很伤心...
You know, at first I was really bummed about getting rid of all my stuff.
但是看到你很开心 我就觉得很值
But seeing how happy it makes you-- totally worth it.
我明白你的感受
Mm, that's kind of how I feel when I begrudgingly have sex with you
就像我很累却要勉强做爱时的那样
when I'm really tired.
完全正确 有时候 为了大家应该要妥协
Exactly. Sometimes you gotta take one for the team.
坐下 坐下
Well, sit. Sit, yeah.
你有你前任男友留下的东西?
So you never keep anything your ex-boyfriends gave you?
没有
N ope.
除了我的小狗
Well, except for my dogs.
我丢弃了所有以前女友送我的东西
So I had to get rid of everything from my past relationships
是因为你没有那些东西
because you don't keep things from your past relationships
这5只小狗是从哪里来的?
except, uh, where are your five dogs from? Oh, that's right:
是你前男友们送的
your past relationships.
泰德 你究竟想说什么?
What's your point, Ted?
你说你到我公寓来
Well, you know how you said you come over to my apartment,
不管看到什么都如同 看到我前任女友...
and all you can see are my ex-girlfriends?
你的意思就是说 看见我的小狗 就如同看到了我前任男友?
What, so when you look at my dogs, all you see is my ex-boyfriends?
现在的确如此
I do now.
真是荒谬
That's ridiculous.
我记得你说过 你丢了前任男友送你的所有东西!
I thought you said you got rid of everything your ex-boyfriends gave you.
是的 除了小狗
Well, yeah, but not my dogs.
你说的是所有东西
You said everything.
生物除外
But not living things.
但是我把别人送的仙人掌也扔掉了
Well, tell that to the rare Bolivian cactus I threw away.
那是植物 没有心脏的不包括在内
Things with a heartbeat can stay.
你很开心 是吧?
Enjoying this?
皮卡 去捡你的球
Pickles, go get your ball.
快去
Go get your ball.
认了吧 你有点自私
Just admit it. It was a little hypocritical of you
让我扔掉那些东西
to make me get rid of all my stuff.
好吧 你想让我怎么做? 扔掉我的小狗?
Well, what do you want me to do, Ted? Get rid of my dogs?
我们的位子是不可取代的
Guess what position we did it in.
是的 我想让你扔了这些狗
Yes. Yes, I want you to get rid of your dogs.
不
Um, no.
当真? 如果让大伙来决定的话
Really? Well, I say we take it to the group,
我觉得他们 不会站在你这边的
but I don't like your chances.
她不能扔了她的狗
She's not getting rid of the dogs.
你怎么了?
What's the matter with you?
- 换成我也不会扔 - 的确是这样
- Even I wouldn't do that. - Yes!
你可以要求别人扔了蜥蜴 如果它们爬进你头发里
You can ask somebody to get rid of their iguana after it poops in your hair,
但不能要求扔了他们的狗
but not their dog.
我开始想念占比第恩了
I miss Jebediah.
我差点忘了
Oh, I almost forgot.
我演出的广告宣传单
Flyers for my new play.
真有趣
Very funny.
我不是开玩笑
Oh, it's not a joke.
这是我个人表演的首场演出
It's my one-man show premiering tomorrow night.
虽然演出很烂而且时间会很长
And even though it's terrible and excruciatingly long,
我们是好朋友 我希望你们都去
I expect you all to be there since we're such good friends.
我们会去的
Oh, we'll be there.
除非 你们承认不是...
Unless, of course, you just want to admit that you were wrong...
不会的 太好了
- Never. - Good.
就这样 我去彩排了
Okay, I gotta go rehearse.
忘了提醒你们要带雨衣
Oh, I almost forgot. Bring a poncho;
坐在前三排会被淋湿的
the first three rows get wet.
我很抱歉 没有告诉你狗是哪里来的
I'm sorry I didn't tell you where the dogs came from.
我很抱歉让你把它们扔了
I'm sorry I asked you to get rid of them.
有点不可思议
That was ridiculous.
这么说我们扯平了
So we're-we're okay?
是的 扯平了
Yeah, we're great.
尽管我那么认为
And I thought we were,
但是如同莉莉 戏里第七幕演的那样
but just as it did in the seventh act of Aunt Lily's play,
我还是满怀妒忌
Jealousy reared its ugly head.
真舒服
Oh, yeah, that's the spot.
让开 我要撒尿
Dude, I gotta pee.
我走了
I gotta go.
他真的不喜欢那些狗 是吗?
Oh, he's really having trouble dealing with this, huh?
他真的很不喜欢
Yeah, he really is.
或许我应该把它们扔了
It's got me thinking, maybe I should get rid of my dogs.
或许把它们送到农场去
Might be time to send them to the farm.
- 你打算宰了它们? - 不是 不是
- You're gonna kill your dogs?! - No! No, no, no,
我阿姨有个农场
there really is a farm.
在郊区
My aunt has a farm upstate.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
你知道的 如果我是那5只狗
Aw, you know, if I were five dogs,
我宁可住在农场 而不是市区的公寓里
I'd rather live on a farm than in an apartment in Brooklyn.
我可以周末去看它们
Yeah. I could visit them on weekends.
我阿姨孤孤单单住在农场 而且她很喜欢狗
My aunt is awfully lonely up there. It's just her and her lover, Betty.
那太好了 他们喜欢小狗
Oh, that's perfect. They love dogs.
他们? 你'他们'是什么意思?
"They"? What do you mean by "they"?
嗯...嗯... 郊区的人...
Uh... uh.... uh... People upstate.
演出开始了
Oh, look, it's starting. Shh!
你肯定你还好?
Are you sure you're gonna be okay?
我的意思是 你知道演出会...
I mean, you know that this is gonna be...
但是我会坚持看下去的
I know, but I'm gonna sit through the whole thing,
而且我打算表演 结束后说些好听的
and I'm gonna say something nice about it afterwards.
你知道为什么?
You know why?
因为这是朋友应该做的
Because that's what friends do.
潮湿
Moist.
M oist.
潮湿
Moist.
演出前40分钟都是在说这词
That was the first 40 minutes of Barney's show.
潮湿
Moist.
然后我们忍受了20分钟的这个
And then we endured about 20 minutes of this.
我得去加水了
I have to go refill.
一会就回来
I'll be back in a moment.
表演还没有结束
Play's not over.
从来没有选过我参与演出
I never get picked for audience participation.
它变得更加诡异
And then it just got weird.
感受
Feelings.
内心的感受
Inside.
哦 不
Oh, no!
当那个不奏效时
And when that didn't work...
停下!
Okay! Stop!
你赢了 行吧
You win. Fine.
很抱歉让你去看我的表演
Barney, I'm sorry I made you come to my show.
谢谢 莉莉
Thank you, Lily.
关于我的演出 你还想说点什么?
Is there anything you'd like to say about my show?
无话可说
No.
对于你的表演 我没有什么好话可说的
No, I have nothing nice to say about your show.
你是对的 巴尼
You were right, Barney.
我们去酒吧
Let's go to the bar.
太棒了 我赢了
Yes! I win!
我喜欢胜利
I love winning!
哦 莉莉 哦 莉莉 莉莉
Oh, Lily. Oh, Lily, Lily, Lily.
伙计们 我刚才只是热身
I was just getting warmed up, man!
我猜那会很糟的 我们走
Well, I imagine it was pretty awful, so let's go.
很糟?很糟? 糟糕的事情才刚刚开始
Pretty awful? Pretty awful?! It was a masterpiece of awful.
只有天才才能演得这么糟! 我希望你们继续看下去
It's genius how bad it is. I kind of wish you guys could see it.
无论如何你说的都是对的
Yeah, well, anyway.
第二部分我弄伤了我的腿
Act two is where I really hit my stride.
扰流器改变了方向: 机器人坠入爱河
Spoiler alert: the robot falls in love.
你看这样如何? 我呆在这里
How about this, Barney? How about we stay
看完你剩下的演出?
and-and watch the rest of your show?
你会很痛苦的
It's your funeral.
五 六 一 二
Five, six, one, two.
所以我们又被折磨了一个半小时
So we stayed and let Barney torture us for another hour and a half,
之所以会这样 很显然因为我们是朋友
'cause that's what friends do, apparently.
Hey.
你去哪儿了? 我刚才打电话给你了
Where've you been? I called you earlier.
我把狗送到我阿姨那里去了
I gave my dogs away to my aunt.
什么?
You what?
前段时间是磨合期 但是...
Yeah. Just for a few months as a test run, but...
我认为还是把它们送走为好
I think it's for the best.
啊!
Wow.
真是想不到 亲爱的
Oh, man.
我们进屋吧?
Can we go inside?
啊 不! 我们还是去酒吧好了
Uh, no. Uh, let's go to the bar.
怎么了? 里面发生什么了?
Why? What's going on inside?
- 地板没了 - 什么?
- Um, the floors are gone. - What?
我把它们送去修了
Yeah. I-I sent them out to get, um, fixed.
我撒了谎 我放弃
This is a terrible lie. I'm just going to bail.
我不知道你把狗送走了!
I didn't know you were getting rid of the dogs!
你说过你 把那些东西都扔了的!
You said you threw all that stuff away!
这是我和罗宾 经历的最糟糕的事情
Kids, this was the worst fight Robin and I ever had.
也是能够持续数小时的战争之一
It was one of those fights that last for hours
我们头脑发晕 到后来甚至不知道两个人在吵什么
and you start to get woozy and lose track of what you're fighting about.
我们吵了很久 窗外的季节都变了
We fought for so long, seasons changed outside the window.
日历不停翻页 真是疯狂
Pages of the calendar blew off. It was crazy.
但是最后 我不得不告诉你我的生活如何
But, ultimately, and I couldn't tell you how for the life of me,
以及为什么会变成这样
but somehow we got to here.
我们真要这么做吗?
We're really doing this?
是的
Yeah.
- 我们搬到一块住了 - 我们搬到一块住了
- We're moving in together! - We're moving in together!
机器人觅得了爱情
The robot found love
系统识别错误
Confusing my circuitry
我的系统出现故障
My software's been hacked
吐司烘箱
Toaster oven
是为我准备的
You're the one for me
二 三 四
Two, three, four.
解决问题
That's two.